Guide to the Ellen McGowan Biddle Shipman papers, 1914-1946.
Shipman, Ellen McGowan Biddle papers, 1914-1946.
- Series IV. Project Files (Plans)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Eugene Dupont (Map-case Folder 40-42 and 192)
    - Fill scale drawings of garden door latch, 1928 (Map-case Folder 42)
    - Plan to show paving (Map-case Folder 192)
    - General layout plan (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Planting plan for patio garden (Map-case Folder 192)
    - General design plan for patio gardens (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Topographical plan of property (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Construction plan for steps (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Construction plan and pattern for tile of pool (Map-case Folder 192)
    - General development plan (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Sketch of garden (Map-case Folder 192)
  - William Field (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Construction plan for garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Design plan, 1947 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Contours at house (Blueprint), 1947 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Set of floor plans (Blueprints), 1947 (Map-case Folder 43)
  - Mrs. Robert Franks (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Perennial planting plan for flower garden, 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Shrub planting plan in flower garden, 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Revised construction drawing (Blueprint), 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Construction plan for flower garden, 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Alterations and additions to house, 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Design plan (Black and White), 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Pergola details (Blueprint), 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Construction drawing for pool, 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Trees and shrubs planting plan (Blueprint), 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Design plan, 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
    - Property survey (Blueprint), 1941 (Map-case Folder 43)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Julius Forstmann (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Design plan for garden (Black and White), 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs on boundary, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Location plan for speciman trees, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Detail of limestone fountain coping, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Sketches, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Photostat of first floor plan, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Construction drawing for driveways, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - General construction plan, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Construction plan for south and east terrace, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Revised design plan, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Construction drawing for fountain in forecourt, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Planting plan for entrance court, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Design plan (Blueprint), 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Preliminary design of garden house, 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Drawing of gates for entrance court (Blueprint), 1940 (Map-case Folder 44)
  - Mrs. Stephen Farish (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Sketch for garden house (Map-case Folder 44)
  - R.G. Fessenden (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Fence for drying yard (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 44)
  - Ferry (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Detail of brick paving (Map-case Folder 44)
  - Miss Julia Fish (Map-case Folder 44)
    Location: Greenport, Long Island
    - Details of concrete garden seat, 1916 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Sketch of perennial border, 1916 (Map-case Folder 44)
    - Planting plan of perennial border - Sheets 1, 2, 3, 1916 (Map-case Folder 44)
  - Mrs. A. Gildersleeve (Map-case Folder 45)
    Location: Charlottesville, Virginia
    - Construction drawings for pool (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Construction drawing for garden shelter (Map-case Folder 45)
  - Goodyear (Map-case Folder 45)
    Location: Cornish, New Hampshire
    - Balustrade in garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 45)
  - Phillip Gossler (Map-case Folder 45)
    - General Sketch plan, 1919 (Map-case Folder 45)
      Location: Wheatley Hiils, Long Island
    - Measured drawing of Pergola, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Construction plan for entrance court, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Sketch, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Detail of coping, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Detail of stone coping for pool, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Detail of garden wall construction, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Plan of service yard, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Topography sketch showing driveway entrance, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Details of steps, pool, and terrace, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - General sketch plan, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Plan on host beds and cold frames, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Detail of wrought iron fence, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Construction plan for Spanish wall fountain, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Construction detail of garden gate, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Construction detail of W.I. rail, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Shrub, vine, and bulb planting plan for cottage gardens, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Elevation of garden wall (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Plan of proposed changes in driveway entrance (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Plan of proposed changes in driveway entrance (Map-case Folder 45)
    - General construction plan for gardens, terraces and walls, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Sketch plan for garden, 1925 (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Detail of garden steps (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Bulb plan for center beds in lower gardens (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Bulb plan for upper terrace gardens (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Planting plan for cutting garden (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Shrub plan, undated (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Shrub plan for upper and lower gardens (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Perennial planting plan for upper and lower gardens (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Entrance gate to drying yard (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Detail of fountain in garden (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Detail of garden latch (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Topographic map of estate (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Detail of wooden Balustrade in garden (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Construction plan for root cellars (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Construction plan for garden walls (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Detail of north terrace steps (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Plan of fences at cottages (Map-case Folder 45)
    - Detail of terrace railway (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 45)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Theodore Griffith (Map-case Folder 46)
    Location: Rye, New York
    - Perennial planting plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Shrub and vine planting plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Design plan "A" for flower garden (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Planting plan for picking garden (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Planting plan for shrubs along stone wall (Map-case Folder 46)
    - First floor plan for house (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Construction drawing for gate (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Construction drawing for flower garden (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Construction details pf garden (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Design plan for flower garden Sketch 1, 2, 3, 4 (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Plan of house and garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 46)
    - General trees and shrub plan around cottage (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Design plan for flower garden (Map-case Folder 46)
    - Construction drawing for brick wall (Map-case Folder 46)
  - Mrs. H.V. Greenough (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Bulb planting plan, 1926 (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Sketch elevation of garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Topographical plan (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Revised tree and vine planting plan for wild garden (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Flower planting plan (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Construction deatil for wooden door (Map-case Folder 47)
    - General construction plan and location of walls (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Flower planting plan for wild garden (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Sherub and ground cover planting plan for wild garden (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Construction plan for stone seat (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Construction details for tool house (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Plan for grille opening in recess (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Construction plan for flower garden (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Construction details for walls and terrace (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Construction details for garden (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Details for wall fountain (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Construction plan for lath fence in reserve garden (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Construction details for pool (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Tree and vine planting plan in wild garden (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Construction details for pool (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Sketch plan for showing design of gardens (Map-case Folder 47)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Bowman Gray (Map-case Folder 47)
    Location: Roaring Gap, North Carolina
    - Construction plan for flower garden, 1940 (Map-case Folder 47)
    - Topographical map (Blueprint), undated (Map-case Folder 47)
  - Mr. and Mrs. George P. Greenhalgh (Map-case Folder 48-50)
    Location: Berryville, Virgina ("Springsbury")
    - Construction details for swimming pool (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Blueprints of residence (Map-case Folder 48)
      Floor plans, elevations for house, cottage and barn
    - Proposed sewage system (2 Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Topographic map of estate (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Plan for layout of entrance court and service drive (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Construction drawing for bath houses (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Planting plan for swimming pool area (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Construction drawing for bath houses (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Detail of swimming pool gutter (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Detail of dog watering trough (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Plan of stable road and parking spaces (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Construction drawing of forecourt steps (Map-case Folder 48)
    - Detail of dog watering trough (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Plan of stable road and parking spaces (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Preliminary design plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Revised layout plan of entrance and service drives (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Construction details for entrance walls (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Grading plan for terraces and entrance court (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Revised design plan (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Construction drawing for watering trough in stable court (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Construction plan and details of picket fence (Map-case Folder 49)
    - General planting plan for area around cabin (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Wall sections (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Construction drawings for walls of terraces (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Construction drawings of garage court gate, 1937 (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Full scale drawing of wrought iron post and rail, 1937 (Map-case Folder 49)
    - Full scale drawing for piers in the forecourt, 1937 (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Bulb planting plan for north terrace (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Perennial planting plan for south terrace (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Construction drawing for forecourt walls, 1937 (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Planting plan around Hill House (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Revised drawing for wall and fence in the service court, 1937 (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Tree, shrub, and vine planting plan around house (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Full scale detail of new post and railing on stairs of east terrace, 1937 (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Construction plans for terrace "A" (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Bulb planting plan for south terrace garden (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Details of garden gate (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Construction details of terrace "B" (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Planting plan for forecourt (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Perennial planting plan for north terrace garden (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Full scale drawing of limestone cap for brick piers in forecourt, 1937 (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Full scale drawing of wooden cap for brick gate posts in service court, 1938 (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Location plan of bath house (Map-case Folder 50)
    - Construction drawing for swimming pool terrace, 1945 (Map-case Folder 50)
  - Clare J. Hoffman (Map-case Folder 51)
    Location: Washington Township, Ohio
    - Revised design plan (Map-case Folder 51)
    - Topographic map (2 Black and Whites) (Map-case Folder 51)
    - Design plan for a suburban plot (Map-case Folder 51)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Heorge J. Hanks (Map-case Folder 51)
    Location: Orange, New Jersey
    - Design plan, 1940 (Map-case Folder 51)
    - Design plan, 1944 (Map-case Folder 51)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 51)
  - Mrs. C. Hodson (Map-case Folder 51)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs on boundary, 1941 (Map-case Folder 51)
  - Mrs. Howard Hanna (Map-case Folder 52)
    Location: Kirtland, Ohio
    - Topographic Man (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Construction details for lattice (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Construction drawing for gate and fence (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Preliminary design plan (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Construction plan for garden (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Planting plan for entrance court (Map-case Folder 52)
    - General tree and shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Rough sketch of property (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Grading and road plan (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Topographic Map (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 52)
  - Town Hall (Map-case Folder 52)
    Location: Hunting Valley, Ohio
    - Planting plan (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Revised grades at garages (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Plans and elevations of building (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Proposed development of property (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 52)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Graeme Howard (Map-case Folder 52)
    Location: Mamaroneck, New York
    - General construction plan for swimming pool (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Plot plan (Map-case Folder 52)
    - Preliminary design plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 52)
  - Mr. and Mrs. George Humphrey (Map-case Folder 53-54)
    - Plan for development of the tennis court area (Map-case Folder 53)
    - Detail for stone base of statue (Map-case Folder 53)
    - Construction plan for flagstone terrace (Map-case Folder 53)
    - Plan for location of ditch (Map-case Folder 53)
    - Blueprints of residence (Map-case Folder 53)
    - Topographical map (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 53)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for terraces and around walls (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Topographical survey (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Bulb planting plan for terrace (Map-case Folder 54)
    - General planting plan (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Revised sketch for entrance court (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Preliminary plan for flower border (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Construction plan for flagstone terrace (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Section of entrance court wall (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Details of walls and stops for entrance court (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Perennial planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Planting plan for entrance court (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Tree, shrub, and vine planting plan in garden (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Revised drawing for entrance steps (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Revised design plan for entrance court - Sketch "A" (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Layout plan for first garden - Sketch "B" (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Construction details for wooden seats (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Planting plan for patio (Map-case Folder 54)
    - First floor plan showing location of furniture (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Construction plan for entrance court (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Planting plan for rose garden (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Wrought iron details (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Layout plan for grass terrace and rose beds (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Plan and elevations of wrought iron balustrades (Map-case Folder 54)
    - Second floor plan showing location of furniture (Map-case Folder 54)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Louis Haggin (Map-case Folder 55)
    Location: Versailles, Kentucky
    - Drawing for gate lamp (Map-case Folder 55)
  - Mrs. John Halstead (Map-case Folder 55)
    - Plan for location of apple trees (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 55)
    - Plan of residence (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 55)
    - Topographic Map (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 55)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs along road (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 55)
    - Construction details of wall and gate (Map-case Folder 55)
    - Planting plan for front entrance (Map-case Folder 55)
    - Sketch of suggested drive layout (Map-case Folder 55)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Gordon Hanes (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Plan for roadside planting (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Perennial planting plan (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Planting plan for picking garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Construction drawing for house terrace (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Design plan for box garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Planting plan for shrubs and vines (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Design plan (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Plot plan (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Topographic map (2 copies of Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Shrub planting plan of garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Map showing topography and trees (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 56)
    - plan of planting and retaining wall of front of house (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Bamboo trellis for rose garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Construction details of pool and garden steps (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Revised planting for rose beds (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Perennial planting plan for pear tree walk (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Plan of location of rose arches (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Tree, shrub, and vine planting plan for pear tree walk (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Plan for additional shrubs and vines (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Perennial planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - General construction plan for garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Bulb planting plan for upper garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Bulb planting plan for lower garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Perennial planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Perennial planting plan for upper garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Planting plan for perennial garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - planting plan for tulips in garden (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Planting plan for front entrance (Map-case Folder 56)
    - Details for rose arch (Map-case Folder 56)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Robert Hanes (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Details for Millstone birdbath (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Construction plan for garden - Sheet 1 (Map-case Folder 57)
    - General design plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Topographic map of garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Construction details for pools - A and B (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Construction plan for tree seat (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Details of tea house (x2) (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Sections of tea house (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Paving plan in tea house (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Plan of tea house (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Elevation of tea house (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Details of brick paving in garden (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Details of oak seat in tea house (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Perennial planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Bulb planting plan for terrace (Map-case Folder 57)
    - General planting plan for terrace (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Blulb planting plan for rose garden (Map-case Folder 57)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 57)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Christian Herter (Map-case Folder 58)
    Location: Millis, Massachusetts
    - Construction details for arbor (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Construction drawing for trellis (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Preliminary design plan (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Topographic plan of property (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 58)
  - Julian H. Harris (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Revised layout plan (Map-case Folder 58)
    - General design plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Construction plan for gate (Map-case Folder 58)
    - General tree planting plan (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Garden layout plan (Map-case Folder 58)
    - plan of land in Nantucket (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Contour plan of Harris land (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Layout of parking space and picket fence (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Sketch of entrance drive (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Revised layout plan of road and parking space (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Location plan of house and garage (Map-case Folder 58)
    - Details of fence (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 58)
  - Mr. and Mrs. P.H. Hanes (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Details of brick design at center of paved terrace (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Details of garden house - Sheets 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Bulb planting plan for flower borders (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Wall fountain (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Revisions of flower garden - Sketch "A" (2 copies) (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Construction details for pool (Map-case Folder 59)
    - General design plan, undated (Map-case Folder 59)
    - General construction plan (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Planting plan for standards in small garden (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Construction details for wall and pool (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Perennial planting plan for small garden (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Bulb planting plan for small garden (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Sketch of stand for potted plants (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Revisions of flower garden (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Perennial planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Elevations of garden house - Sheet 1 (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Elevations of garden house - Sketches (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for area around gardens (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Elevation of top of gate (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Revisions of flower garden - Sketch "B" (2 copies) (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Construction drawing for wrough iron rose arches (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Construction details for central pool (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Revised perennial plan for small garden (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Design for knot garden (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Foundation plan of garden house (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Lilac planting plan (Map-case Folder 59)
    - Annual and dahlia planting plan for small garden (Map-case Folder 59)
  - Judge and Mrs. Hudson (Map-case Folder 60)
    Location: Sault Sainte Marie, Michigan
    - Plan for staking out road (Map-case Folder 60)
    - Construction plan for paved terraces and walk (Map-case Folder 60)
    - Revised dimensions for terrace (Map-case Folder 60)
    - Construction plan of flower garden (Map-case Folder 60)
    - General design plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 60)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 60)
    - Bulb planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 60)
    - Perennial planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 60)
    - General tree and shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 60)
    - Construction drawing for pool (Map-case Folder 60)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 60)
  - Ralph P. Hanes (Map-case Folder 61-62)
    - Revised construction drawing for pergola (Map-case Folder 61)
    - Details of pergola (Map-case Folder 61)
    - Revised construction plan for upper garden (Map-case Folder 61)